<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources >
    <string name="app_name">inso</string>
    <string name="menu">菜单范例</string>
    <string name="menu_key">范例</string>
    <string name="menu_intent">Intent Menu</string>
    <string name="time_day">天</string>
    <string name="time_hour">时</string>
    <string name="time_min">分</string>
    <string name="alarm_time_min">分钟</string>
    <string name="time_sec">秒</string>
    <string name="menu_worldtime">世界时间</string>
    <string name="menu_intervalremind">间隔提醒</string>
    <string name="menu_vipremind">来电提醒</string>
    <string name="menu_alarmclock">闹钟</string>
    <string name="A01">米家石英表</string>
    <string name="A02">电池剩余</string>
    <string name="time_still_adjust">继续校准</string>
    <string name="A03">%</string>
    <string name="A04">电池电量低查看详情</string>
    <string name="A05">今天步数\n</string>
    <string name="A06">\t步</string>
    <string name="A08">连接失败,点击重试</string>
    <string name="A09">设备连接中,请稍候...</string>
    <string name="A10">连接失败,请检查网络后再试</string>
    <string name="B01">电池电量</string>
    <string name="B02">已使用</string>
    <string name="B03">耗电比例</string>
    <string name="B04">计时</string>
    <string name="B05">振动提醒</string>
    <string name="B06">计步</string>
    <string name="B07">数据传输</string>
    <string name="B08">剩余电量</string>
    <string name="unit_step">\t步</string>
    <string name="unit_km">\t千米</string>
    <string name="unit_kc">\t千卡</string>
    <string name="unit_hour">\t时</string>
    <string name="unit_min">\t分</string>
    <string name="unit_second">秒</string>
    <string name="unit_min1">分钟</string>
    <string name="unit_min2">分钟</string>
    <string name="unit_ge">个</string>
    <string name="unit_ren">人</string>
    <string name="empty_tip_worldtime">还没有添加城市</string>
    <string name="title_worldtime">世界时间</string>
    <string name="title_setalarm">设置闹钟</string>
    <string name="button_ok">确定</string>
    <string name="button_repeat">重复</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">取消</string>
    <string name="have_used">已使用</string>
    <string name="off">未开启</string>
    <string name="interval_off">每隔一段时间，手表将提醒</string>
    <string name="interval_tip">每隔%1$d分钟时间，手表将振动提醒</string>
    <string name="interval_tip_one">每隔%1$d分钟时间，手表将振动提醒</string>
    <string name="interval_integral_tip">每到整点，手表将振动提醒</string>
    <string name="interval_tip_default">每隔一段时间，手表将振动提醒</string>
    <string name="dfu_success_exit">升级成功，请退出插件重新连接</string>
    <string name="power_enough">电量充足</string>
    <string name="power_lower_tip">电量低,请注意更换电池</string>
    <string name="dfu_file_download_fail">无法下载升级包，请检查网络</string>
    <string name="unit_year">年</string>
    <string name="unit_year_space">\t年</string>
    <string name="unit_month">月</string>
    <string name="unit_month_space">\t月</string>
    <string name="unit_day">日</string>
    <string name="unit_week">周</string>
    <string name="alarm">闹钟</string>
    <string name="world_time">世界时间</string>
    <string name="vip_alert">来电提醒</string>
    <string name="interval_remind">间隔提醒</string>
    <string name="alarm_empty_tip">还没有添加闹钟，无法提醒\n最多可添加10个</string>
    <string name="please_select_item">请选择项目</string>
    <string name="alarm_most_tip">最多可添加10个闹钟</string>
    <string name="city_most_tip">最多可添加10个城市</string>
    <string name="contact_most_tip">最多可添加10个联系人</string>
    <string name="less_than_one_minute">不到1分钟振动</string>
    <string name="one_hour">小时</string>
    <string name="how_many_hours_ring">后振动</string>
    <string name="morning">上午</string>
    <string name="afternoon">下午</string>
    <string name="please_select_city">请选择城市</string>
    <string name="btn_complete">完成</string>
    <string name="adjust_time_ing">正在调整时间</string>
    <string name="time_has_adjusted">时间已调整</string>
    <string name="adjust_time_fail">时间调整失败，请重试</string>
    <string name="adjust_time_to_beijing">正在调整为北京时间</string>
    <string name="adjust_time_to_tw">正在调整为台北时间</string>
    <string name="adjust_time_to_hk">正在调整为香港时间</string>
    <string name="ble_connect_off">手表连接已断开，请重新连接</string>
    <string name="unit_fenzhong">分钟</string>
    <string name="set_interval_duration">设置间隔时间</string>
    <string name="adjust_ponit">指针校准</string>
    <string name="body_info">身体信息</string>
    <string name="set_birthday">出生年月</string>
    <string name="set_gender">性别</string>
    <string name="nv">女</string>
    <string name="nan">男</string>
    <string name="setHeight">身高</string>
    <string name="unit_limi">厘米</string>
    <string name="unit_gongjin"> 公斤</string>
    <string name="unit_gongjin_space"> \t公斤</string>
    <string name="set_weight">体重</string>
    <string name="device_info">设备信息</string>
    <string name="settting">设置</string>
    <string name="vibrationsetting">振动设置</string>
    <string name="start_time">开启时间</string>
    <string name="end_time">结束时间</string>
    <string name="please_select_contact">请选择联系人</string>
    <string name="setting_waiting">设置中，请稍候...</string>
    <string name="setting_complete">设置完成</string>
    <string name="vip_empty_tip">无联系人,无法提醒\n最多可添加10个联系人</string>
    <string name="sorry_not_support_vip">抱歉，您的手机暂不支持此功能\n目前仅支持苹果和小米手机MIUI9以上</string>
    <string name="no_contact_permission">没有联系人权限，请前往系统设置页面开启应用读取联系人权限。</string>
    <string name="adjust_time_point">校准计时指针</string>
    <string name="have_adjusted">已校准</string>
    <string name="adjust_step_point">校准计步指针</string>
    <string name="adjust_step_tip">滑动下方滚轮,\n使计步指针指示到0</string>
    <string name="guide_birthday">出生年月</string>
    <string name="guide_tip">为了保证运动数据准确，请核对以下信息</string>
    <string name="pass">跳过</string>
    <string name="next_step">下一步</string>
    <string name="guide_height">身高</string>
    <string name="last_step">上一步</string>
    <string name="recovery_tip">是否下载您以前的\n手表设置？</string>
    <string name="download_setting">下载设置</string>
    <string name="neednot">不用了</string>
    <string name="guide_gender">性别</string>
    <string name="guide_weight">体重</string>
    <string name="vip_error">该米家应用版本暂不支持来电提醒功能，请升级米家应用。</string>
    <string name="repeat">重复</string>
    <string name="alert_double">振动时长加倍</string>
    <string name="notdisturb">免打扰时段</string>
    <string name="birthday">出生年月</string>
    <string name="gender">性别</string>
    <string name="height">身高</string>
    <string name="weight">体重</string>
    <string name="search_city">搜索城市</string>
    <string name="name">名称</string>
    <string name="model">型号</string>
    <string name="firmware">固件</string>
    <string name="ble">蓝牙</string>
    <string name="battery">电池</string>
    <string name="set_interval_time">设置间隔时间</string>
    <string name="reset_interval">重新计时</string>
    <string name="search_contact">搜索联系人</string>
    <string name="have_no_content">没有搜索到匹配的内容</string>
    <string name="integral">整点</string>
    <string name="low_power_title">手表电量低</string>
    <string name="ignore">忽略</string>
    <string name="close_vibration">关闭振动</string>
    <string name="low_power_msg">振动提醒会拉低电压，有可能会造成\n手表意外关机(需换电池后手动校准时间)，\n您是否需要关闭振动以延长使用时间？</string>
    <string name="retype">重新输入</string>
    <string name="adjust_sure">校准</string>
    <string name="adjust_time_first_tip">滑动下方滚轮,使手表上的分针\n指在临近整点刻度,点击下一步</string>
    <string name="what_is_time">输入手表上指示的时间,\n而非当前标准时间</string>
    <string name="adjust_warning_tip">您应该输入手表时间,而不是标准时间</string>
    <string name="format_date_no_year">MM月d日</string>
    <string name="format_date_month">M月</string>
    <string name="useragreement_privacypolicy">使用条款和隐私政策</string>
    <string name="user_agreement">用户协议</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">隐私条款</string>
    <string name="watch_pick_hour">时</string>
    <string name="watch_picker_minute">分</string>
    <string name="open_ble_tip">当前蓝牙未开启，请先开启蓝牙？</string>
    <string name="allow">确定</string>
    <string name="reject">取消</string>
    <string name="button_delete">删除</string>
    <string name="watch_select_all">全选</string>
    <string name="watch_unselect_all">全不选</string>
    <string name="loading_wait">数据加载中,请稍候...</string>
    <string name="read_fail">读取数据失败</string>
    <string name="watch_log">手表日志</string>
    <string name="test_watchlog">实验功能-手表日志</string>
    <string name="connect_no_sure">无法连接？</string>
    <string name="connect_timeout_msg">请尝试以下方法：\n1.将手表靠近手机，按一下手表按键\n2.重启手机蓝牙或手机\n3.换新手机连接手表时，请先关闭之前手机的蓝牙\n更多建议请在使用帮助中查看</string>
    <string name="connect_know">确定</string>
    <string name="btb_close_vibrate">关闭振动</string>
    <string name="btn_ignore">忽略</string>
    <string name="tip_only_once">为了延长使用时间,手表会在低电时自动关闭振动。\n您可以在\"更多-振动设置\"中修改。</string>
    <string name="reject_switch">当前电量低,无法开启振动功能。</string>
    <string name="label_close_auto">低电时自动关闭振动功能</string>
    <string name="low_power_reject_upgrade">当前电量不足以安全升级固件，请更换电池后再试</string>
    <string name="exit_wait">退出中，请稍侯...</string>
    <string name="img_bottom_tip">点击滚轮可以微调指针</string>
    <string name="current_ver">当前版本:</string>
    <string name="upgrade_success">更新成功</string>
    <string name="upgrade_ing">更新中...</string>
    <string name="upgrading_tip">手表固件更新中,请勿退出\n待升级成功后即可使用</string>
    <string name="pls_set_pos">请输入手表的指针位置</string>
    <string name="h_hand_position">时针位置</string>
    <string name="m_hand_position">分针位置</string>
    <string name="deal_with_accurate_pos">不确定分针精确位置怎么办？</string>
    <string name="tap_to_exact_mark">点击转针按钮,\n让分针对齐整刻度</string>
    <string name="move_hand">转针</string>
    <string name="calibrate">校准</string>
    <string name="tap_calibrate">点击校准按钮, 指针会自动转到正确时间</string>
    <string name="reference_step_hand">手表步针显示的是概要步数，每走大约400步，\n步针才会行进一格</string>
    <string name="xx_00">点击校准按钮, 步针会自动指向当前准确步数</string>
    <string name="xx_01">点击或长按转针按钮，转动\n步针，通过不断点按，\n使步针指向0刻度</string>
    <string name="xx_03">步针未动怎么回事?</string>
    <string name="xx12">例如，手表指针显示为10点8分左右时，\n请把分针转到10点10分</string>
    <string name="dfu_call_user_upgrade">当前固件版本有问题，请尽快升级最新固件！</string>
    <string name="dfu_fail">升级失败</string>
    <string name="n_12s">为恢复手表的正常使用\n请长按按键12s重启手表</string>
    <string name="action_more">更多</string>
    <string name="add">添加</string>
    <string name="inshow_protocol">
&lt;p id="en"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software License and Service Agreement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Notice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inso Technology Co., Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as &quot;Inso&quot;) hereby reminds the user to carefully read and
        fully understand the Software License and Service Agreement (this &quot;Agreement&quot;). &lt;strong&gt;The user shall
        carefully read and fully understand the terms of this Agreement, in particular those relating to the exemption
        or limitation of Inso\'s liability, dispute resolution and applicable laws.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Your attention is
        drawn to the terms relating to the exemption or limitation of liability, which have been marked in bold. Please
        read carefully and choose to accept or not accept this Agreement (a minor should be accompanied by his/her legal
        guardian while reading this Agreement). By downloading, installing and using the software, as well as obtaining
        and logging in your account, you agree to accept this Agreement and to be fully bound by its terms.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inso reserves the right to amend this Agreement. Updated terms of this Agreement will be published on the
        official website or software, and become effective from the date of publication.&lt;/strong&gt; The user can re-download
        and install the software or view the latest version of the terms of this Agreement on the website. &lt;strong&gt;After
        Inso has amended the terms of this Agreement, if you do not accept the amended terms, please immediately
        discontinue using of the &quot;Mi Quartz Watch&lt;/strong&gt;&quot; &lt;strong&gt;software and services provided by Inso;
        the user\'s continued use of the &quot;Mi Quartz Watch&quot; software and services provided by Inso will be
        deemed acceptance of the amended terms of this Agreement.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. General Provisions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.1. This Agreement is the agreement concluded by and between you (hereinafter referred to as the &quot;User&quot;)
        and Inso and its operation partner (hereinafter referred to as the &quot;Partner&quot;) concerning the User\'s
        downloading, installation and use of the &quot; Mi Quartz Watch&quot; software (hereinafter referred to as the
        &quot;Software&quot;) of Inso and use of relevant services of Inso.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.2. The Software and services are provided by Inso for installation on (including but not limited to) mobile smart
        terminal devices, mainly for users to view the step-counting data, modify relevant information (such as body
        information, device name), and set up for functions like call reminder, alarm clock, etc.) Mi and upgrade watch
        firmware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1.3. The ownership and right-to-operate of the Software and services shall be vested in Inso.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Scope of Software Licensing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.1. Inso grants the User a personal, non-transferable and non-exclusive license to use the Software without the
        right to sublicense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.2. The User can install, use, display and run the Software on a single mobile terminal device for non-commercial
        purposes. However, the User shall not install, use or run the Software for commercial operation purposes. The User
        shall not copy, alter or modify any data of the Software, or any data released to the memory of any terminal device
        during the running of the Software and the interactive data generated between the client and the server during the
        running of the Software, or run the Software with plug-ins, or create any derivative work in any form, including but
        not limited to plug-ins, access to the Software and related systems through unauthorized third-party tools/services.
        If you need to sell, copy or distribute the Software commercially, e.g. software pre-installation and bundling, you
        must obtain the written authorization and license from Inso. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.3. Without the permission of Inso, the User shall not install the Software on other terminal devices that are not
        expressly permitted by Inso, including but not limited to set-top boxes, game consoles, televisions, DVD players and
        so on. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.4. The User may make a copy of the Software for the purpose of using the Software and services, but it shall be
        used only as a backup. The backup copy must contain all the copyright information contained in the original
        software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.5. Except as expressly authorized by this Agreement, Inso does not grant other rights to the User. If the User
        intends to use any other right, the written consent from Inso shall be obtained in advance. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Software Acquisition, Installation and Upgrading&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.1. The User shall download and install the Software from the website or in the manner designated by Inso. Be aware
        not to download the Software on unspecified websites, so as to prevent mobile devices from infecting malicious
        programs that can destroy user data and acquire user privacy information. If you acquire the Software or the
        installation program with the same name as the Software from a third party that has not been authorized by Inso,
        Inso cannot guarantee it will be used normally and Inso accepts no liability for any loss thereby caused to you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.2. The User must select the Software version that matches the terminal device installed. Otherwise, any software
        problems, device problems or damages resulting from mismatch between the Software version and the device model shall
        be solely assumed by the User.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.3. In order to improve User experience and optimize service content, Inso reserves the right to provide replaced,
        modified and upgraded version of the Software, and also reserves the right to charge for such replacement,
        modification or upgrading, but will obtain your consent in advance for such charges. The Software will enable &quot;upgrade
        prompt&quot; feature by default for the User. Depending on the Software version used by the User, Inso provides the
        User with the discretion to or not to enable the said feature. After the new version of the Software is released,
        Inso does not guarantee that older versions of the Software will continue to be usable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Usage Specifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.1. The User may use the Software and services in accordance with this Agreement and laws. The User shall
        not commit the following acts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.1. Delete any copyright information on the Software and other copies, or modify, delete or circumvent the
        technical measures set by the Software for the protection of intellectual property rights; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.2. Perform reverse engineering of the Software, such as disassembly, decomplication or other attempts to obtain
        the source code of the Software;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.3. Add, remove or change the features or running effects of the Software by modifying or forging the instructions
        and data during the running of the Software, or otherwise operate or disseminate to the public the software or
        methods used for the purposes described above, whether or not for commercial purposes;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.4. Use the Software to commit any acts detrimental to network security, including but not limited to: using
        unauthorized data or access to unauthorized servers/accounts; unauthorized access to public networks or the
        operating system of others and delete, modify or add any information stored; unauthorized attempts to detect, scan
        or test the Software system or network weaknesses or do other things that destruct network security; attempt to
        interfere with or destruct the normal operation of the Software system or website, deliberately spread malicious
        programs or viruses, or carry out other acts that destruct or interfere with normal network information services;
        forge the name or partial names of TCP/IP data packet;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.5. The User logs in or uses the Software and services through third party compatible software or systems not
        developed, authorized or approved by Inso, or makes, publishes or disseminates the above tools;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.6. Without the written consent of Inso, the User does anything on the Software or the information contained
        therein, including but not limited to using, leasing, lending, copying, modifying, setting up a link, reproducing,
        compiling, releasing, publishing, establishing a mirror image website, or unauthorized use of the Software to
        develop related derivative products, works, services, plug-ins, compatibility or interconnection;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.7. Use the Software to publish, transmit, disseminate or store any content that violates local laws and
        regulations; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.8. Use the Software to publish, transmit, disseminate or store any content that infringes the legitimate rights
        such as intellectual property rights and trade secrets of others; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.9. Use the Software to publish, transmit or disseminate advertising information or spam in bulk; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.1.10. Use the Software and other services provided by Inso, in any unlawful manner, for any unlawful purpose or in
        any manner inconsistent with the licensed usage under this Agreement;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.2. Information Publication Specifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.1. You may use the Software to publish information such as views, data, text, information, user names, pictures,
        photos, personal information, audio or video files, links and so on that are created by you or that you have the
        right to publish. You must guarantee that you have the intellectual property rights or you have obtained the legal
        authorization of the information uploaded by you, and that your use of the Software and services does not infringe
        any legitimate rights or interest of any third party.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.2. While using the Software, you are required to comply with local laws and regulations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.3. You shall not use the Software to commit the following acts, including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.3.1. Produce, reproduce, publish, disseminate or store any of the following contents that violate local laws and
        regulations:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.3.2. Publish, transmit, disseminate or store any content that infringes the legitimate rights such as reputation
        right, portrait right, intellectual property rights and trade secrets of others;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.3.3. Make up the fact or conceal the truth to mislead or deceive others;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.3.4. Publish, transmit or disseminate advertising information or spam;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.3.5. Engage in other acts that violate local laws and regulations and so on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;4.2.4. Without the permission of Inso, you shall not carry out any commercial conduct in the Software, such as
        advertising, selling merchandise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.3 You understand and agree that:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.3.1. Inso will determine whether the User is suspected of violating the above-mentioned usage
        specifications and, based on the result of such determination, suspend or terminate the use license granted to you
        or take other restrictive measures that may be taken in accordance with this Agreement;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.3.2. Inso will directly delete any information suspected of being unlawful or infringing the legitimate
        rights of others or violating this Agreement, which is published by the User during use of the licensed
        Software;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.3.3. If you violate the above-mentioned usage specifications and thus cause damages to third parties, you
        need to assume the liability in your own name independently and to hold Inso harmless from and against any loss or
        expense arising therefrom;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4.3.4. The User shall indemnify and hold harmless Inso from and against any and all losses, third-party
        claims, administrative penalties, damages and/or expenses, including reasonable attorney fees, investigation and
        evidence collection costs, incurred or suffered by Inso resulting from the User\'s violation of relevant laws or
        breach of this Agreement.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Privacy Policy and Personal Data Protection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.1. It is important for Inso to protect your personal data. In order to provide the Software features and improve
        User experience, Inso will collect the following types of data:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5.1. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information you provide to us or
        upload&lt;/strong&gt;: we may collect personal information you provide to us, like&lt;a &gt;&lt;/a&gt; your gender,
        height, weight, step counting data, watch settings (e.g. your alarm setting, vibration setting, device name, time
        zone, contact names in the Call Reminder) and feedbacks that you may sync through Mi Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5.2. Information specific to you that may be assigned by us&lt;/strong&gt;: we may collect and use information such
        as your Mi Account ID.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.2. We collect, use and protect your data in accordance with our Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy is available on
        the following website www.insolife.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5.3. &lt;strong&gt;We may from time to time share with Xiaomi the data related to Xiaomi / Mi / Mitu brands and services,
        in order to provide and improve the exciting products and services (including software and hardware) from Xiaomi and
        Xiaomi Ecological Chain, and offer better features and user experience.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Service Risk and Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;6.1. The User must procure the device required for Internet access and the usage of telecom value-added services by
        the mobile terminal device, and bear the communication fees, information fees and related costs incurred by Internet
        access of personal mobile terminal device or charged by third parties (including but not limited to
        telecommunications and mobile communication providers). If any telecom value-added services are needed, you are
        advised to confirm the costs with your telecom value-added service provider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6.2. Neither Inso nor its Partner is liable for any loss suffered by the User due to reasons attributable to
        third parties such as communication line failure, technical problem, network or mobile terminal device failure,
        system instability and other various force majeure factors.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6.3. The Software, like most other Internet software, may be affected by factors including but not limited to
        user reasons, network service quality, social environment differences, etc., and may also be subject to the
        harassment relating to various security problems, such as the usage of data of the User by others, resulting in
        harassment in real life; other software downloaded and installed by the User or other websites visited by the User
        contain &quot;Trojan horse&quot; and other viruses, threatening the security of the User\'s terminal device
        information and data, and then affecting the normal use of the Software. The User shall enhance the awareness of
        information security and user data protection, and pay attention to strengthening password protection, so as to
        avoid loss and harassment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6.4. When the User uses the Software or requests Inso to provide specific services, the Software may call a
        third-party system or software to support the User\'s use or access. The results of the use or access will be
        provided by the third party. Inso does not guarantee the safety, accuracy and effectiveness of the results achieved
        through the support of the said system or software, nor does Inso assume any other uncertain risks; if any dispute
        or damage is caused thereof, Inso will not assume any liability.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6.5 Inso specifically draws the User\'s attention to that, in order to protect the company\'s business
        development and adjustment autonomy, Inso has the right to modify or suspend the services at any time without notice
        to the User and without any liability to the User or any third party.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6.6. Except as expressly provided in laws and regulations, we will do our utmost to ensure that the Software
        and the technology and information involved are safe, effective, accurate and reliable; however, subject to the
        existing technology, the User understands that Inso cannot guarantee it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6.7. The User shall be solely liable for any personal injuries or incidental or consequential damages,
        including but not limited to loss of profit, loss of data, business interruption or other commercial damages arising
        out of or in connection with: (1) the use or failure to use the licensed Software; (2) unauthorized use of the
        Software or modification of the User\'s data by a third party; (3) costs and losses incurred by the User during use
        of the Software; (4) misunderstanding by the User of the Software; (5) other losses in connection with the Software
        for reasons not attributable to Inso.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6.8. In the event of any personal or economic damages or losses that have been or may be caused due to the
        conduct performed by the User and other software users through any software, or due to the User\'s being misled or
        deceived, the faulting party shall assume all liabilities arising thereof.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Statement on Intellectual Property Rights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.1. Inso is the intellectual property right holder of the Software. All intellectual property rights such as
        copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, etc. relating to the Software, and all information related to the
        Software (including but not limited to text, pictures, audio, video, graphics, interface design, layout, data or
        electronic documents, etc.) are protected by local laws and regulations and corresponding international treaties.
        Inso enjoys the above intellectual property rights, except for Xiaomi / Mi / Mitu trademark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;7.2 Without the prior written consent of Inso, the User shall not independently use or transfer any of the above
        intellectual property rights for any commercial or non-commercial purposes, or permit any third party to do so. Inso
        reserves the right to pursue legal liability for such acts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Amendment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8.1. Inso reserves the right to amend the terms of this Agreement from time to time at its sole discretion,
        and any such amended terms will be timely published on relevant web pages. If you do not agree to any amendment, you
        shall take the initiative to cancel the services. If you continue to use the services, it shall be deemed your
        acceptance of the amended Agreement. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8.2. Inso or the Partner reserves the right from time to time and at its sole discretion to modify or change
        the paid services provided, the charging criteria, charging mode, service charges or service terms. In providing the
        services, Inso may start to charge some users for certain fees now or in the future. If the User refuses to pay such
        fees, the User will not be able to continue using relevant services after the charging starts. &lt;/strong&gt;Inso and the
        Partner will do their utmost to notify the User of any amendments or changes by email or otherwise. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. Applicable Law and Dispute Resolution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9.1. The validity and interpretation of this Agreement shall be governed by the laws of the Mainland of the People\'s
        Republic of China. In the absence of relevant legal provisions, reference may be made to international business
        practices and/or business practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;9.2. This Agreement is signed in Nanshan District, Shenzhen, China. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9.3. Both the User and Inso agree that any dispute arising from the services shall first be settled through
        consultations by the Parties. If no settlement can be reached through such consultations, either Party may submit
        the dispute to the court of competent jurisdiction over the place where this Agreement is signed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10. Miscellaneous&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10.1. For any specific service of the Software, there may be a separate agreement and related business rules, etc.
        (hereinafter collectively referred to as the &quot;separate agreement&quot;), so please read and agree to relevant
        separate agreement before using such specific service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10.2. This Agreement shall enter into force on the 10th day of January, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10.3. The headings to all the terms of this Agreement are for ease of reference only and shall be ignored in
        interpreting this Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10.4. If any provision of this Agreement is or becomes invalid or unenforceable for whatever reasons, the remaining
        provisions hereof shall remain in full force and effect and binding upon both Parties hereto.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inso&lt;/p&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="inshow_privacy">
&lt;p id="privacy_en"&gt;PRIVACY POLICY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Update!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Privacy Policy was updated on 26 July 2018. We have revamped the Privacy Policy front and back so that from this
        date onwards, this Privacy Policy can provide privacy details on how we manage your personal information for Mi
        Quartz Watch applications and services provided by Inso.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please take a moment to familiarise yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any
        questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OUR COMMITMENT TO YOU&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Privacy Policy sets out how Inso Technology Co., Ltd. collect, use, disclose, process and protect any
        information that you give us when you use our products and services located at www.insolife.com, Mi Quartz Watch
        applications that we offer. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when
        using Mi Quartz Watch applications and services, it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy and/or
        our terms and conditions for users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Privacy Policy is designed with you in mind, and it is important that you have a comprehensive understanding of
        our personal information collection and usage practices, as well as full confidence that ultimately, you have
        control of any personal information provided to Inso.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this Privacy Policy, &quot;personal information&quot; means information that can be used to identify an
        individual, either from that information alone or from that information combined with other information Inso has
        access about that individual. Such personal information may include but not limit to your name, address, telephone
        number and email address.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By using Mi Quartz Watch applications and services, you are deemed to have read, acknowledged and accepted all the
        provisions stated here in the Privacy Policy, including any changes we may make from time to time. We are committed
        to protecting the privacy, confidentiality and security of your personal information by complying with applicable
        laws, including your local data protection legislation. We are equally committed to ensuring that all our employees
        and agents uphold these obligations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, what we want is the best for all our users. Should you have any concerns with our data handling practice
        as summarised in this Privacy Policy, please contact our Data Protection Officer at privacy@inshowlife.com to
        address your specific concerns. We will be happy to address them directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED AND HOW DO WE USE IT?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to provide our services to you, we will ask you to provide personal information that is necessary to provide
        those services to you. If you do not provide your personal information, we may not be able to provide you with our
        products or services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may collect the following types of information (which may or may not be personal information):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information you provide to us or upload&lt;/strong&gt;: we may collect personal information you provide to us, like&lt;a
        &gt;&lt;/a&gt; your Mi Account ID, gender, height, weight, step counting data. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information specific to you that may be assigned by us&lt;/strong&gt;: we may collect and use information such as
        your watch settings, e.g. your alarm setting, vibration setting, device name, time zone, contact names in the Call
        Reminder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other information&lt;/strong&gt;: feedbacks that you may sync through Mi Cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HOW THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IS USED&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal information is collected for providing services and / or products to you, and legal compliance on our part
        under applicable laws. You hereby consent that we may process and disclose personal information to our affiliated
        companies (which are in the communications, social media, technology and cloud businesses), Third Party Service
        Providers (defined below) for the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may use your personal information for the following purposes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Providing, processing, maintaining, improving and developing our goods and/or services to you, including
        after-sales and customer support and for services on your device or through our websites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Communicating with you about your device, service or any general queries, such as updates, customer inquiry
        support, information about our events, notices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are more details on how we use your information (which may include personal information): &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Syncing information (Mi Account ID, step counting data, alarm setting, vibration setting, device name, time
        zone, contact names in the Call Reminder) when user switches between different mobile devices.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collecting your gender, height, weight to make activity data (Calorie consumption and mileage) more accurate.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collecting feedbacks to improve user experience of the product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DIRECT MARKETING&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may use your name, phone number, and email address, Mi Account ID and IMEI number to provide marketing materials
        to you relating to goods and services of Inso and our business partners which offer network, mobile applications and
        cloud products and services. We will only so use your personal data after we have obtained your consent or
        indication of no objection in accordance with local data protection laws, which may require separate explicit
        consent. You have the right to opt out of our proposed use of your personal data for direct marketing. If you no
        longer wish to receive certain types of email communications you may opt-out by following the unsubscribe link
        located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at privacy@inshowlife.com. We will not transfer your
        personal data to our business partners for use by our business partners in direct marketing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES (ONLY WHEN BROWSING WWW.INSOLIFE.COM)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What information is collected and how do we use them? Technologies such as cookies, tags, and scripts are used
        by Inso and our Third Party Service Providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering
        the site, tracking users’ movements around the website and to gather demographic information about our user base
        as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as
        well as aggregated basis.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Log Files: As true of most websites, we gather certain information and store it in log files. This information
        may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit
        pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected
        data to other information we gather about you.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advertising: We partner with our Third Party Service Providers to either display advertising on our website or
        to manage our advertising on other sites. Our Third Party Service Provider may use technologies such as cookies
        to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising
        based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose
        of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile Analytics: Within some of our mobile applications we use mobile analytics software to allow us to better
        understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as
        how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance
        data, and where crashes occur within the application. We do not link the information we store within the
        analytics software to any personal information you submit within the mobile application.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WITH WHO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not sell any personal information to third parties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may disclose your personal information on occasion to third parties (as described below) in order to provide the
        products or services that you have requested.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disclosure may be made to Third Party Service Providers and affiliated companies listed in this section below. In
        each case described in this section, you can be assured that Inso will only share your personal information in
        accordance with your consent. You should know that when Inso shares your personal information with a Third Party
        Service Provider under any circumstance described in this section, Inso will contractually specify that the third
        party is subject to practices and obligations to comply with applicable local data protection laws. Inso will
        contractually ensure compliance by any Third Party Service Providers with the privacy standards that apply to them
        in your home jurisdiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHARING WITH OUR GROUP AND THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to conduct business operations smoothly in providing you with the full capabilities of our products and
        services, we may disclose your personal information from time to time to other Inso affiliated companies (in
        communications, social media, technology or cloud businesses), or our third party service providers which are our
        mailing houses, delivery service providers, telecommunications companies, data centres, data storage facilities,
        customer service providers, advertising and marketing service providers, and Inso’s representatives. Such Third
        Party Service Providers would be processing your personal information on Inso’s behalf or for one or more of the
        purposes listed above. If you no longer wish to allow us to share this information, please contact us at
        privacy@inshowlife.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHARING WITH OUR GROUP’S ECOSYSTEM COMPANIES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xiaomi works together with a cool group of companies, which together form the Mi Ecosystem. The Mi Ecosystem
        companies are independent entities, invested and incubated by Xiaomi, and are experts in their fields. Inso may
        disclose your personal data to the Xiaomi or other Mi Ecosystem companies so as to provide you with and improve the
        exciting products and services (both hardware and software) from the Mi Ecosystem. Some of these products and
        services will still be under the &lt;strong&gt;Xiaomi / Mijia/ Mitu brands&lt;/strong&gt;, while others may use their own brand.
        Inso will take appropriate organizational and technical measures to ensure the security of personal data during the
        process of sharing of information, including but not limited to the encryption of your personal data. If Inso is
        involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email
        and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any changes in ownership, uses of your personal information, and
        choices you may have regarding your personal information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SHARING WITH OTHERS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inso may disclose your personal information without further consent when required under applicable law.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INFORMATION NOT REQUIRING CONSENT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We may share anonymised information and statistics in aggregate form with third parties for business purposes, for
        example with advertisers on our website, we may share them trends about the general use of our services, such as the
        number of customers in certain demographic groups who purchased certain products or who carried out certain
        transactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the avoidance of doubt, Inso may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your consent if it is
        and only to the extent it is allowed explicitly under local data protection laws. Such disclosure may be brought
        about by the necessity to protect our rights, ensure the safety of you and other people, and comply with the
        requirements of the local government to facilitate the investigations of illegal activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SECURITY SAFEGUARDS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;INSO’S SECURITY MEASURES&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are committed to ensuring that your personal information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access,
        disclosure or other similar risks, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to
        safeguard and secure the information we collect from your using of Inso products and services and on Inso websites.
        We will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, when you access your Mi Account, you can choose to use our two-step verification process for better
        security. When you send or receive data from your Inso device to our servers, we make sure they are encrypted using
        Secure Sockets Layer (&quot;SSL&quot;) and other algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All your personal information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. We classify
        your data based on importance and sensitivity, and ensure that your personal information has the highest security
        level. We make sure that our employees and Third Party Service Providers who access the information to help provide
        you with our products and services are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be
        disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet such obligations. We have special access controls for cloud-based
        data storage as well. All in all, we regularly review our information collection, storage and processing practices,
        including physical security measures, to guard against any unauthorised access and use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will take all practicable steps to safeguard your personal information. However, you should be aware that the use
        of the Internet is not entirely secure, and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any
        personal information which is transferred from you or to you via the Internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WHAT YOU CAN DO&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can play your part in safeguarding your personal information by not disclosing your login password or
        account information to anybody unless such person is duly authorised by you. Whenever you log in as a Mi Account
        user on Inso websites, particularly on somebody else\'s computer or on public Internet terminals, you should
        always log out at the end of your session.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inso cannot be held responsible for lapses in security caused by third party accesses to your personal
        information as a result of your failure to keep your personal information private. Notwithstanding the
        foregoing, you must notify us immediately if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other Internet
        user or any other breach of security.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your assistance will help us protect the privacy of your personal information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RETENTION POLICY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal information will be held for as long as it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which it was collected, or
        as required or permitted by applicable laws. We shall cease to retain personal information, or remove the means by
        which the personal information can be associated with particular individuals, as soon as it is reasonable to assume
        that the purpose for which that personal information was collected is no longer being served by retention of the
        personal information, including the cases when the personal information is no longer required for resolving legal
        disputes, applying our Agreements, or achieving our business goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the personal information on the device (except for the current time and current number of steps as showed on the
        device) will be erased when you hard reset your device. To implement a hard-reset function, you can withdraw your
        consent in Mi Home app, then press the watch button for 12s to reset the watch. (Note that the watch will not
        therefore stop working.) Beware that hard-reset can’t be undone, so you have to make sure that you don’t need the
        information any more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACCESSING OTHER FEATURES ON YOUR DEVICE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our applications may need access to certain features on your device such as Wi-Fi network status This information is
        used to allow the applications to run on your device and allow you to interact with the applications. At any time
        you may revoke your permissions by turning these off at the device level or contacting us at
        privacy@inshowlife.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;YOU HAVE CONTROL OVER YOUR INFORMATION!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CONTROLLING SETTINGS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inso recognises that privacy concerns differ from person to person. Therefore, we provide examples of ways Inso makes
        available for you to choose to restrict the collection, use, disclosure or processing of your personal information
        and control your privacy settings: for example, log in and out of the Mi Account. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for the abovementioned purposes, you may change
        your mind at any time by writing or emailing us at privacy@inshowlife.com.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ACCESS, UPDATING, CORRECTING OR ERASURE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You have the right to request access to and/or correction of any other personal information that we hold about
        you. When you update your personal information, you will be asked to verify your identity before we proceed with
        your request. Once we obtain sufficient information to accommodate your request for access to or correction of
        your personal information, we shall proceed to respond to your request within any timeframe set out under your
        applicable data protection laws.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We normally provide such services for free but reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee for your data access
        request.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you would like to request access to your personal data held by us or if you believe any information we are
        holding on you is incorrect or incomplete or if you believe any information we are holding on you is
        inappropriate or excessive, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the email address below. Email:
        privacy@inshowlife.com.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For details relating to the personal information in your Mi Account, you may also access and change them at
        http://account.mi.com or by logging into your account on your device.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;WITHDRAWAL OF CONSENT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You may withdraw your consent for the collection, use and/or disclosure of your personal information in our
        possession or control by submitting a request. This may be done by clicking “User Agreement and Privacy Policy”
        in the “General settings” menu of Mi Home app or sending e-mail to privacy@inshowlife.com. We will process your
        request within a reasonable time from when the request was made, and thereafter not collect, use and/or disclose
        your personal information as per your request.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Please recognise that your withdrawal of consent could result in certain legal consequences. Depending on the
        extent of your withdrawal of consent for us to process your personal information, it may mean that you will not
        be able to enjoy Inso’s products and services.
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TRANSFER OF PERSONAL INFORMATION OUTSIDE OF YOUR JURISDICTION&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To the extent that we may need to transfer personal information outside of your jurisdiction, whether to our
        affiliated companies (which are in the communications, social media, technology and cloud businesses) or Third Party
        Service Providers, we shall do so in accordance with the applicable laws. In particular, we will ensure that all
        transfers will be in accordance with requirements under your applicable local data protection laws by putting in
        place appropriate safeguards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inso may use overseas facilities operated and controlled by Inso to process or back up your personal information.
        Currently, Inso has data centres in Beijing and Singapore. These overseas jurisdictions may or may not have in place
        data protection laws which are substantially similar to that in your home jurisdiction. We may transfer to and store
        your personal information at our overseas facilities. However, this does not change any of our commitments to
        safeguard your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MISCELLANEOUS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MINORS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We consider it the responsibility of parents to monitor their children’s use of our products and services.
        Nevertheless, it is our policy not to require personal information from minors or offer to send any promotional
        materials to persons in that category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inso does not seek or intend to seek to receive any personal information from minors. Should a parent or guardian
        have reasons to believe that a minor has provided Inso with personal information without their prior consent, please
        contact us to ensure that the personal information is removed and the minor unsubscribes from any of the applicable
        Inso services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ORDER OF PRECEDENCE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have agreed to our applicable User Agreements, in the event of inconsistency between such User Agreements and
        this Privacy Policy, such User Agreements shall prevail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We keep our Privacy Policy under regular review and may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our
        information practices. If we make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by email (sent to the
        e-mail address specified in your account) or post the changes on all the Inso websites or through our software, so
        that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it. Such changes to our Privacy Policy shall
        apply from the effective date as set out in the notice or on the website. We encourage you to periodically review
        this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of products and services on the
        websites, mobile phones and/or any other device will be taken as acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy. We will
        seek your fresh consent before we collect more personal information from you or when we wish to use or disclose your
        personal information for new purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DO I HAVE TO AGREE TO ANY THIRD PARTY TERMS AND CONDITIONS?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Privacy Policy does not apply to products and services offered by a third party. Inso products and services may
        include third parties’ products, services and links to third parties’ websites. When you use such products or
        services, they may collect your information too. For this reason, we strongly suggest that you read the third
        party’s privacy policy as you have taken time to read ours. We are not responsible for and cannot control how third
        parties use personal information which they collect from you. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to other sites
        linked from our services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SOCIAL MEDIA (FEATURES) AND WIDGETS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our websites include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this
        button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you
        are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social media features and
        Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our websites. Your interactions with these Features
        are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SINGLE SIGN-ON&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on your jurisdiction, you may be able to log in to our website using sign-on services such as Facebook
        Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you the option to share
        certain personal information (such as your name and email address) with us, and to pre-populate our sign up form.
        Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this website to your
        profile page to share with others within your network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CONTACT US&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or any questions relating to Inso’s collection, use
        or disclosure of your personal information, please contact our Data Protection Officer at the address below
        referencing &quot;Privacy Policy&quot;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inso Technology Co., Ltd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1004, Jinqi Zhigu Building, Chongwen Garden, Liuxian Avenue, Nanshan District, &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shenzhen, China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email: privacy@inshowlife.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for taking the time to understand our Privacy Policy!&lt;/p&gt;
    </string>
    <string name="on">已开启</string>
    <string name="vip_change_ota">来电提醒功能已优化升级，请更新固件后使用</string>
    <string name="incoming_tip_top">已开启\n为保证功能正常，请不要关闭手机蓝牙</string>
    <string name="incoming_center_tip">开启后,手机来电时手表会振动提醒\n此功能会加速电量消耗</string>
</resources>